This Christmas get elevated by love
Merry Kissmas is a comedy, romance, tv movie film directed by Michael Feifer.
Unwinding her relationship from a controlling choreographer, Kayla happens
to take an elevator ride with lonesome caterer “Dustin”.
The lift stalls, and spontaneously, magical kisses follow.
Soon the choreographer makes nice, and Dustin retreats.
Kayla becomes confused as to which man to love.
Kayla, played by Karissa Lee Staples.
Dustin, played by Brant Daugherty.
Carlton, played by David O'Donnell.
Kim, played by Brittany Underwood.
Jana, played by Ion Overman.
Mrs. Joyner, played by Roxanne Hart.
Brittany Underwood (born July 6, 1988) is an
American actress, director, and singer.
She is known for her roles as teenagers Langston Wilde on the daytime soap opera One Life to
Live and Loren Tate on the Nick at Nite/TeenNick serial drama Hollywood Heights.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.